Guide to The Packer Collegiate Institute records 2014.019
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 8: Student Life, 1837-2016
  - Sub-series 8.7: Diplomas and Scholarship Certificates, 1840s-1952; 1 Cubic Feet in three boxes
    - Diploma of Cornelia Hinsdale from Brooklyn Female Academy, 1854 (Box 105, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Carol Francis Jacobs, 1940 (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Ophelia Marle (?) from Brooklyn Female Academy (with seal), 1854 (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Diploma and teaching certificate of Harriet S. Mead, 1850s (Box 159, Folder -)
      Mead was a member of the Brooklyn Female Academy Class of 1853.
    - Diploma of Cornelia M. Olcott from Brooklyn Female Academy, 1854 (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Mary Emma Peck, 1902 (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Alice Elizabeth Recknagle, 1929 (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Anita M.L. Simonson, 1894 (Box 105, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Katharine Mead Sloan, 1898 (Box 105, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Marjorie R. Smith, 1914 (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Joy Corinne Stevenson, 1891 (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Phebe A. Wickham from Brooklyn Female Academy, 1848 (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Diploma of Sarah E. Wickham, 1861 (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Blank Diplomas from Brooklyn Female Academy, 1840s-1850s (Box 550, Folder -)
    - Blank Diplomas from Brooklyn Female Academy (rolled), 1840s-1850s (Box 42, Folder -)
    - Blank Diplomas From Packer Institute, circa 1880s-1900s (Box 550, Folder -)
- Series 9: School Events, 1846-2015
  The series contains items related to school events (commencements, Class Days, anniversaries, etc.) and daily diaries which record events and other day-to-day matters at Packer, dating from 1846 to 2015.
  Additional event programs can be found in Sub-series 11.1: Administrative files, Sub-series 12.4: Curriculum files, Sub-series 12.10: Alumni Questionnaires, and Sub-series 12.15: Alumni Association Geographic Chapters.
  Programs for Packer theatrical performances are filed in Sub-series 8.3: Packer Theater.
  Additional files relating to commencements are available in Sub-series 12.5: Graduation files.
  Items relating to Alumni Events are filed in Sub-series 12.14: Alumni Events and Sub-series 12.15: Alumni Association Geographic Chapters.
  Photographs of events can be found in Series 17: Photographs and audiovisual recording of events can be found in Series 18: Audio, film, and video recordings.
  The series is organized into two sub-series:
  Sub-series 9.1: Event programs and ephemera
  Sub-series 9.2: Event diaries
  - Sub-series 9.1: Event programs and ephemera, 1846-2015; 7 Cubic Feet in twenty four boxes
    The sub-series contains programs and ephemera relating to events at Packer, dating from 1846 to 2015. It include commencements, Class Days, Founders Days, dedications, concerts, anniversaries, and other school sponsored events.
    It includes a small amount of items relating to the Brooklyn Female Academy.
    - Brooklyn Female Academy opening invitation and published handwritten address by William B. Sprague, 1846 (Box 466, Folder 21)
    - Address by William B. Sprague delivered at the opening of the Brooklyn Female Academy, 1846 (Box 566, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Female Academy commencement program, 1847 (Box 466, Folder 22)
    - First Grand Concert of the Misses Bruck and M. Butterworth, 1852 (Box 466, Folder 23)
      2007 reproduction
    - Founder's Day: Various essays and clippings about the history of Packer, 1854 (Box 379, Folder 6)
      Booklet, "The Packer Collegiate Institute," titled, Education of Females from November 9. The booklet gives the school's perspective on Women's Rights.
    - Reverend Francis Vinton, D.D. delivers Founding Address to the community: "Celebration of Pre-Opening of the Packer Collegiate Institute for the Education of Females in the City of Brooklyn", 1854 (Box 158, Folder 9)
      Includes manuscript invoice of archives Minard LaFeven
    - Address of Reverend Francis Vinton, D.D. celebrating the opening of Packer Collegiate Institute, 1854 (Box 566, Folder 9)
    - School Dedication Celebration Invitation, 1854 (Box 119, Folder 35)
    - Commencement announcements, Newspaper Article, 1856-1933 (Box 157, Folder 23)
    - Commencement Program, 1857 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Commencement Program, 1858 (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Commencement invitations, 1858-1870 (Box 466, Folder 24)
    - Commencement Program, 1859 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Historical Cantata (5 programs), 1859 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Commencement Program, 1863 (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - Commencement clipping, 1864 (Box 466, Folder 25)
    - Women in History, An Entertainment given by the Senior class of the Packer Institute in Aid of the Brooklyn and Long Island Sanitary Commission in the Chapel of the Institute (4 programs), 1864 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Mock commencement program, circa 1865 (Box 466, Folder 26)
    - Handwritten commencement program and printed entertaining, music, and readings program, 1866 (Box 466, Folder 27)
    - Commencement Program, 1866 (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - Commencement Exercise Invitations: 1922, 1924, 1925, 1929, 1932, 1933, Concert and Commencement at Collingwood Opera House Invitation, 1869 June, 1869-1933 (Box 119, Folder 36)
    - Commencement Program, 1870 (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - Commencements, Class Days, and other events, 1870s (Box 466, Folder 28)
    - Commencement Program, 1873 (Box 120, Folder 21)
    - Commencement announcement, 1874 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Commencement Program, 1874 (Box 120, Folder 22)
    - Address, October 22, 1874 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Commencement Program, 1875 (Box 120, Folder 23)
    - Commencement Program, 1876 (Box 120, Folder 24)
    - Address, June 29, 1876 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Class Day Booklets, 1876-1898 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Commencement Program, 1878 (Box 120, Folder 25)
    - Address, March 1, 1880 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Commencements, Class Days, and other events, 1880s (Box 466, Folder 29)
    - The Efficiency of Refinement, A Sermon, by Rev. Henry M. Booth, D.D. (2 pamphlets), 1881 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Commencement Program, 1882 (Box 120, Folder 26)
    - Commencement Program, 1883 (Box 120, Folder 27)
    - Commencement Program, 1884 (Box 120, Folder 28)
    - Commencement and Class Day articles, 1885 (Box 466, Folder 30)
    - A Baccalaureate Sermon to the Class of 1886 and the Class of 1888 (2 pamphlets), 1886-1888 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Baccalaureate Sermons, 1886-1899 (Box 157, Folder 28)
    - Glee Club, dances, and theatrical performances, 1890s (Box 467, Folder 1)
    - Alfred Noyes lecture invitation, circa 1890s (Box 467, Folder 2)
    - Class Day Programs, 1889, 1897-1898 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Commencement and Class Day, 1890 (Box 467, Folder 3)
      Includes petition regarding commencement
    - Commencement, Class Day, Louisa Richardson event, 1891 (Box 467, Folder 4)
    - Class Day, 1892 (Box 467, Folder 5)
    - Commencement, Class Day, and World's Fair fundraising event, 1893 (Box 467, Folder 6)
    - Commencement Program, 1893 (Box 120, Folder 29)
    - Commencement and Class Days, 1894-1896 (Box 467, Folder 7)
    - Commencement Program, 1896 (Box 120, Folder 30)
    - 1 commencement program, 3 commencement invitations, and 1 commencement ticket, 1896 (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - Class Day and Commencement Program, 1896-1909 (Box 566, Folder 6)
    - Commencement Program, 1897 (Box 120, Folder 31)
    - Commencement Program, 1898 (Box 120, Folder 32)
    - Commencement and Class Days, 1898 (Box 467, Folder 8)
    - Commencement and Class Day clippings, 1898 (Box 467, Folder 9)
    - Class Day and Baccalaureate sermon, 1899 (Box 467, Folder 10)
    - Commencement Program, 1899 (Box 120, Folder 33)
    - Commencement and Class Days, 1900-1904 (Box 467, Folder 11)
    - Golden Jubilee—Pledges—Programs—Correspondence, 1902-1903 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Golden Jubilee, 1903 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Golden Jubilee - 50th Anniversary, 1903 (Box 467, Folder 12)
    - Golden Jubilee – Concert Program, 1903 (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - Golden Jubilee – Concert Program, 1903 (Box 118, Folder 28)
    - Jubilee calendars, 1903 (Box 363, Folder 5)
    - Jubilee Calendars 1853-1903 (Box 534, Folder -)
    - Commencement Program, 1904 (Box 120, Folder 34)
    - Glee Club, dances, concerts, and theatrical performances, 1904-1922 (Box 467, Folder 13)
    - Commencements and Class Days, 1905-1913 (Box 467, Folder 14)
    - Ceremony of the unveiling of the windows erected in the chapel in memory of Crittenden and Eaton program, 1906 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - Ceremony of the unveiling of the windows erected in the chapel in memory of Crittenden and Eaton program, 1906 (Box 467, Folder 15)
    - Ceremony of the unveiling of the windows erected in the chapel in memory of Crittenden and Eaton program, 1906 (Box 566, Folder 7)
    - Commencement Program, 1907 (Box 120, Folder 35)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1907 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Commencement Program, 1908 (Box 120, Folder 36)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1908 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1909 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Thanksgiving clipping, 1909 (Box 467, Folder 16)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1910 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Concert for the benefit of the Endowment Fund of The Packer Collegiate Institute at the Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1910 (Box 566, Folder 7)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1911 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Founder's Day Program, 1911-1915 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Founder's Day, 1911-1934 (Box 156, Folder 32)
    - Founder's Day: Programs for Founder's Day 1911 and 1930-57, 1911-1957 (Box 379, Folder 7)
      Includes alumni "Invitations to Tea" to celebrate Founders Day.
    - Gymnasium Exercise Invitation, 1912 (Box 119, Folder 38)
    - M. Anatole Le Braz Conference, Written in French, 1912 (Box 119, Folder 37)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1912 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - School Exhibit Invitation, 1913 (Box 119, Folder 39)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1913 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Commencement, Class Day, and Senior-Junior debate, 1914 (Box 467, Folder 17)
    - Invitations to Annual Exhibit, 1914 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1914 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Class Day Booklets, 1914-1915 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Commencement Program, 1914-1915 (Box 120, Folder 37)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1915 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Invitations to Annual Exhibit, 1915-1919 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Commencements and Class Days, 1915-1919 (Box 467, Folder 18)
    - Mr. & Mrs. Edward Goodwin Class of 1916 Invitation (Box 119, Folder 41)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1916 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Commencement Program, 1917 (Box 120, Folder 38)
    - "Red Cross Fair" Invitation, 1917 (Box 119, Folder 40)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1917 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Class Day Booklets, 1917-1925 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1918 (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1919 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Seventh Annual Exhibit invitation, 1919 (Box 467, Folder 19)
    - Commencements, Class Days, and annual sermon, 1920-1923 (Box 467, Folder 20)
    - Invitations to Annual Exhibit, 1920-1924 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Chapel Exercise Invitation, circa 1920s (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - "Centenary Celebration" in honor of John Keats Invitation, circa 1920s (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Dr. & Mrs. Paul David Shafer Reception Invitation, circa 1920s (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Edward Jasper Goodwin Commemorative Meeting Invitation, circa 1920s (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - "England and the U.S. in Recent Times" Lecture Invitation, circa 1920s (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Mr. John Denbigh & Miss Denbigh Senior Class Reception Invitation, circa 1920s (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Oral English Department "Poetry Recital" Invitation, circa 1920s (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Principle John H. Denbigh Reception Invitation, circa 1920s (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1921 (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1922 (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - "Gathering of Parents" and Parent Meeting Invitations, 1922-1924 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Address Delivered by Frederick P. Bellamy, 1923 (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Commencement Program, 1923 (Box 120, Folder 39)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1923 (Box 119, Folder 22)
    - Commencement, Class Day, Founders Day, 1924 (Box 467, Folder 21)
    - Class Day program, 1924 (Box 566, Folder 6)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1924 (Box 119, Folder 23)
    - Women's Club invitations, 1924 (Box 467, Folder 22)
    - Commencement, Class Day, and meeting of Denbighs with seniors, 1925 (Box 468, Folder 1)
    - Glee Club Concert Invitation, 1925 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Parents League of Brooklyn – Conference, 1925 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1925 (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - Invitations to Annual Exhibit, 1925-1929 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Commencement and luncheon, 1926 (Box 468, Folder 2)
    - Founders Day correspondence, 1926 (Box 468, Folder 3)
    - Parents League of Brooklyn – Conference, 1926 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1926 (Box 119, Folder 25)
    - "Two Conferences" at the Brooklyn Women's Club January 13th and January 25th Invitation, 1926 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Class Day Booklets, 1926-1930 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Class Day Invitations, 1926-1945 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Commencement, Class Day, Founders Day, and Glee Club concert, 1927 (Box 468, Folder 4)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1927 (Box 119, Folder 26)
    - Commencement Program, 1928 (Box 120, Folder 40)
    - 75th Anniversary - Printed dinner seating arrangement November 9, 1928, Dinner Invitation in Envelope with Print of the School – Printed booklet on the history of Packer from 1853 – 1928 with Portraits of School Principals (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - 75th Anniversary Invitation and Mailer, 1928 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - 75th Anniversary Program, 1928 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - 75th Anniversary Dinner seating arrangement, 1928 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - 75th Anniversary Fund – Dinner Committee, 1928 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Commencement and Class Day, 1928 (Box 468, Folder 5)
    - Diamond Jubilee - 75th Anniversary, 1928 (Box 468, Folder 6)
    - Diamond Jubilee – 75th Anniversary Song, 1928 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Diamond Jubilee dinner ephemera, 1928 (Box 566, Folder 7)
    - Diamond Jubilee song, 1928 (Box 468, Folder 7)
    - Diamond Jubilee song sheet music, 1928 (Box 534, Folder -)
    - Diamond Jubilee seating arrangements, 1928 (Box 468, Folder 8)
    - Diamond Jubilee history booklets, 1928 (Box 468, Folder 9)
    - Diamond Jubilee speeches, 1928 (Box 468, Folder 10)
    - Founder's Day Program – 75th Anniversary, 1928 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1928 (Box 119, Folder 27)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1929 (Box 119, Folder 28)
    - Commencements, 1929-1936 (Box 468, Folder 11)
    - Founder's Day Hymns, circa 1930s (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Cooperative Educational conference, 1930 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1930 (Box 119, Folder 29)
    - Invitations to Annual Exhibit, 1930-1934 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1931 (Box 119, Folder 30)
    - Edward Jasper Goodwin celebration, circa 1931 (Box 468, Folder 12)
    - Class Day Booklets, 1931-1934 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Founder's Day Program, 1931-1936 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Invitations to Teas, Musical Evenings, Luncheons, Amateur Night, Memorial Service, and Committee Reports, 1931-1943 (Box 381, Folder 2)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1932 (Box 119, Folder 31)
    - Packer Athletic Association annual dinners, 1933, 1942 (Box 468, Folder 13)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1933 (Box 119, Folder 32)
    - Founders Day clipping, 1934 (Box 468, Folder 14)
    - Frank L. Babbot portrait presentation - address by Rev. L. Mason Clarke, 1934 (Box 468, Folder 15)
    - Eightieth anniversary of the dedication of the school, 1934 (Box 468, Folder 16)
    - History tribute of the Class of 1884 – Booklet, 1934 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1934 (Box 119, Folder 33)
    - Class Day Booklets, 1935-1937 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Twenty-fourth Annual Exhibit of Work, 1936 (Box 468, Folder 17)
    - John H. Denbigh address to PTA, 1936 (Box 468, Folder 18)
    - PTA Address, 1936 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Founder's Day Invitations, 1936-1940 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Dr. Denbigh honorary tea party, 1937 (Box 468, Folder 18)
    - Graduation clippings, 1937 (Box 468, Folder 19)
    - Invitations to Annual Exhibit, 1937-1940 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - The Packer Choral Winter Concert programme, 1938 (Box 566, Folder 7)
    - PTA Address, 1938 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - Class Day Booklets, 1938-1940 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Founders Day speech by Ruth Benedict, 1939 (Box 468, Folder 20)
    - PTA Address, 1939 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - "PTA Book Pageant" Invitation, 1939 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Sermon to Graduating Class, 1939 (Box 119, Folder 34)
    - PTA Address, 1941 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - Class Day Booklets, 1941-1943 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Class Day, 1942-1945 (Box 468, Folder 21)
    - College Day, 1943 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Commencement Program, 1943 (Box 120, Folder 41)
    - Centennial Committee, 1943-1945 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - College Day, 1945 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Conference on Education and the Faith of America invitations and programs, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 1)
    - Education and the Faith of America conference transcripts, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 2)
    - Centennial addresses - "Education and the Faith of America", 1945 (Box 469, Folder 3)
    - Centennial addresses - "Education and the Faith of America", 1945 (Box 566, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Bulletin and Publication, 1945 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Centennial programs and schedules, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 4)
    - Centennial pageant programs, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 5)
    - Centennial pageant typescript, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 6)
    - Centennial dinner programs, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 7)
    - Centennial dinner programs and invitations, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 8)
    - Centennial dinner fundraising speech, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Book of Plans, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 10)
      One copy includes inserts of Centennial dinner program, speech, celebration program, chapel service program, Centennial hymn, pageant program, 1948 annual fund mailing, words to hymns
    - "A Long Way Forward" circulars, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 11)
    - Centennial circulars, 1945 (Box 469, Folder 12)
    - Centennial dinner transcripts, 1945 (Box 470, Folder 1)
    - Special Centennial bulletin issues by the Alumnae Association, 1945 (Box 470, Folder 2)
    - Centennial hymn, 1945 (Box 470, Folder 3)
    - Centennial notes, 1945 (Box 470, Folder 4)
    - Centennial poetry(?), 1945 (Box 470, Folder 5)
    - Commencements, 1945-1946 (Box 470, Folder 6)
    - Centennial Fund Drive, 1945-1949 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - College Day, 1946 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Commencement Program, 1946 (Box 120, Folder 42)
    - College Day, 1947 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - PTA Address, 1947 (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - 49ers' Fair, 1949 (Box 470, Folder 7)
    - College Day, 1949 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Symposium on the Liberal Arts, 1951 (Box 470, Folder 8)
    - Mildred McAfee Horton lecture, 1953 (Box 470, Folder 9)
    - Founders Day, 1954 (Box 470, Folder 10)
    - List of photographs shown by Dr. Shafer at the PTA dinner, 1956 (Box 470, Folder 11)
    - Commencement Program, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 43)
    - Founders Day, 1957 (Box 470, Folder 12)
    - Parent-Teacher Association Annual Meeting program, 1957 (Box 566, Folder 7)
    - Dedication of Katharine Sloan Pratt Hall, 1958 (Box 470, Folder 13)
    - Dedication of Katherine Sloan Pratt Hall, 1958 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Packer County Fair, circa 1960s (Box 470, Folder 14)
    - Junior College commencements, 1960-1972 (Box 470, Folder 15)
    - Founder's Day: Alumni Associates Invitations for Special Events for Founders Day, 1960-1979 (Box 379, Folder 8)
      Includes invitations, programs, poems, songs, alumni lists, press releases, press clipping, committee notes on budget and arrangement.
    - Packer Programs – Publications, 1966-1987 (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - Address at the conclusion of the 122nd year of The Packer Collegiate Institute by Paul David Shafer, 1967 (Box 566, Folder 9)
    - Class Day (1 pamphlet), 1967 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Class Day (cancelled), 1968 (Box 470, Folder 16)
    - John Skillman 125th anniversary remarks, 1970 (Box 470, Folder 17)
    - Founder's Day: Speeches by Jane Rinden, 1978 (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - Founder's Day November 8 – Various receipts, expenses, memos, minutes., 1979 (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clipping Re: May Queen, circa 1979 (Box 470, Folder 18)
    - Founder's Day November 13 – Various letters, receipts, memos., 1980 (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - Garden party and auction program, 1981 (Box 470, Folder 19)
    - President Peter Esty welcoming ceremony, 1982 (Box 470, Folder 20)
    - Graduation of John Frosch Skillman, Jr., 1982 (Box 470, Folder 21)
    - Women's History Week celebration, 1982 (Box 470, Folder 22)
    - Invitation PTA sp. Garden party publication (2 copies), 1983 (Box 382, Folder 7)
    - Parent Teacher Association spring garden party, 1983 (Box 470, Folder 23)
    - Graduation programs and invitations, 1989-2006 (Box 470, Folder 24)
    - J. Geoffrey Pierson installation ceremony, 1990 (Box 470, Folder 25)
      Installation ceremony program, 1990
    - Miscellaneous Programs, Plays and Various School Activities., 1990s (Box 382, Folder 8)
    - Former Trustees reception, 1992 (Box 470, Folder 26)
    - Pumpkin Patch festival program, 1995 (Box 470, Folder 27)
    - Promotional postcard for Stephan Koplowitz Company dance-theater performace at Packer, 1995 (Box 471, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, 1996 (Box 471, Folder 2)
    - Sesquicentennial celebration, 1996 (Box 471, Folder 3)
    - Sesquicentennial celebration memorabilia, 1996 (Box 471, Folder 4)
    - Sesquicentennial celebration t-shirt, 1996 (Box 471, Folder 5)
    - Founders Day, 1996 (Box 471, Folder 6)
    - Pratt Theater Rededication programs and invitations, 1999 (Box 471, Folder 7)
    - Pumpkin Patch festival weekend, 1999 (Box 471, Folder 8)
    - Academic awards program, 2001 (Box 471, Folder 9)
    - Commencement, 2001 (Box 471, Folder 10)
    - Campus dedication ceremony, 2003 (Box 471, Folder 11)
      Related digital photographs and video available
    - Event programs and invitations to dedications and celebrations, 2003-2007 (Box 471, Folder 12)
    - Earth Day Celebration, 2004 (Box 471, Folder 13)
      Includes student work
    - Carol Shen Gallery opening, 2004 (Box 471, Folder 14)
    - Postcard and Program, Geoff Pierson 14th Anniversary Celebration, 2004 (Box 471, Folder 15)
      Includes Fourteen Years of Leadership program and invitation, 2004
    - Promotional materials for Picasso@Packer and Alumni artists exhibits in Carol Shen Gallery, 2004 (Box 471, Folder 16)
      Artists include Derek Buckner (class of 1988) and Patty Catuera (class of 1981)
    - Promotional materials for Harvey Stein photography exhibit in Carol Shen Gallery, 2005 (Box 471, Folder 17)
    - Promotional materials for "Night Goblins" by Megumi Nagai exhibit in Carol Shen Gallery, 2005 (Box 471, Folder 18)
    - Cordy Ryman '90 "School Daze" exhibit in Carol Shen Gallery - promotional materials and list of works, 2005 (Box 471, Folder 19)
    - "a look inside..." DVD release celebration invitation, 2005 (Box 471, Folder 20)
      Includes copy of DVD